1,2,3,start!
Three, two, one, go!
Good morning.
I'm sorry about the Chinese tags.
Please take a good picture.
I put your name in the picture.
I'm not wearing any clothes, so the manager, Mr. Tang tag...
Mr. Tang tag.
I'll do my best.
Good morning.
Good morning. Today's key point is the lip.
I'm using an unusual pink color today, so I hope you will pay attention to the lips.
I'll do my best!
Good morning.
Good morning. This is Master. We will begin the rehearsal.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Q. What are your goals for this year?
We have been working on it since last year, but we had to make some changes, such as the formation of four members.
But we have already worked hard on a tight schedule since the end of the 5 member concert, so I think we will be fine.
I think we will be fine.
Q. What is your goal for this year?
So my face is bigger than usual.
I don't have to do it too much.
Today we don't have MC until the last song, so I thought I couldn't leave my sense of touch.
I couldn't leave my sense of touch.
I'm just trying to get into the spirit of the show.
I'll do my best!
Hello everyone.
I love encores!
Coming from a catty Kokoro.
Looks like kokoro to me.
Midwinter feathers echo
Love for a hundred thousand thousand years
dyed by the earth
Angels
Lady to Poverty
You make a Poverty
Only the snow is white
Often and Often
When the moon falls, in my dreams
I want to eat meat with you
When it's time to take over me and go
If you're beyond free
The dream will last forever
If only I could say I want to go back
I'd like to go back
then
Well, that's all for now, we're done with the rehearsal.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you all day.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Rehearsal has just finished.
Oh, it's gone.
He's gone, he's gone. Bye-bye.
What a surprise. I was so surprised that I pretended I didn't see it just now.
What's the hardest thing about today?
The two hardest things today are to do 16 songs in a row and to change clothes in 3 minutes.
I wonder if I can make it in 3 minutes.
But today is the first time since I became an idol that I haven't been nervous at a one-man show, so I feel like I'll be fine.
I'll do my best!
I'm going to be nervous.
Nervousness is my enemy, so I'll relax and do my best.
I cracked. I've cracked.
I'm absolutely sure, today.
I was the only one flying early. Rehearsal.
The usual.
Worked hard.
I enjoyed it.
I'm looking forward to it so much.
I'll do my best.
It's okay, it's okay.
Let's change it up with cameras and style.
One by one who can throw up as soon as we stop by.
Ellie for Nanase, Yurika for Versamik Burn!
In the kitchen, please.
That's it, and we're done, because we've already had enough this time.
We're done.
That's it!
Thank you for watching!
Let's keep up the good work!
Regret sonst
final work billing agreement
I love to love it
so good it's still toasty
Hey, if you stay forever
I can't say it's far
I really can't, but
But I'm strong
But I...But I
I'm only going to do Sakurai's singles and album leads in the order in which they were written.
I'm going to do them in the order I've given them to you.
I'm going to start from scratch again.
I mean, the four of us are going to do our best
by the way we perform live.
I hope everyone can get the feeling that we're going to do our best
I hope everyone can get that from the way we make our live.
To our dream, to be our dream
I want to make a promise, create an era
What will change now that there are four of us?
We don't have to think too much about it.
It's simple. We've been building up until now.
I wanted to bring out the goodness of this form of Worcester that we've built up over the years.
So the members of Worcester and the staff worked together to come up with the set.
and the staff were thinking about the set together.
I felt the same way.
So it's a simple way to get to know the times of Worcester.
It's also very friendly to newcomers
And for the fans who have known us for a long time
the costumes and the scenery.
I think it's simply interesting.
I hope you will think it's simply interesting.
I was happy to see them at the concert.
Yamamoto
It was really a raging live performance.
For a short period of time
We had to work really hard for the short time we had to put on the show.
I've been thinking about our new position now that we have 4 members.
I'm not sure how I'll feel when I get on stage.
but when we get on stage, I wonder how it will be.
I was anxious that I had to do it right.
I was anxious, but I was having so much fun
But I was having so much fun that all my worries went away.
I think we were able to create a live show where I can honestly say I'm glad to see everyone.
I think we were able to create a live show that people could honestly enjoy and be happy to see.
I am confident that we are making it so that people can honestly enjoy the live show.
I became confident that I could make it so that people can enjoy the live honestly.
Love Complete with Everyone
I wonder if I can sing
I wonder if I can sing.
I'm sure you're right. Destiny.
Someone must be the only one who can beat us
When love is gone for good...
But please, let love come from you.
I'm sure it's true, isn't it?
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Instagram & Twitter Hodori
〜All are welcome!
For once, for the moment.
I thought I'd do this one more time and it's a hell of a hard schedule.
I thought about it on the way.
You thought about it once.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best for the second part.
What a cute customer.
So fun.
I haven't seen fans' faces without masks for a while because of the times we live in, but I still feel that they are trying to communicate with me.
But I still feel that they are trying to communicate with us or answer our questions.
I could tell that they were trying to understand what we were trying to express.
Even though the form of Worst has changed or taken on a new shape, it's still great to know that there are fans like that.
Even if Worst changes its form or takes on a new shape, I felt reassured by the presence of such fans at this live performance.
I want to continue to cherish these people, and I want to do more live shows to entertain them.
I hope that many more people will come to like my shows.
I will do my best!
Bye bye!
Okay, everyone, please do me a favor.
Don't put it in the millimeter box.
Oh, hey, thank you very much.
Be careful.
Yes, sir. Okay.
I found the box under the Calbee.
Got it?
You better fix it where I can't see it.
Millie!
Here!
Nanase!
Millie Cars!
Let's go again!
Great!
I'll be back!
Aww, thank you so much!
I love you
I love you, I love you
I want to enjoy the world
When there's a star, I'm crazy
Near and far I'll take the heat
Every night, the night sees
Midsummer's blue sky
Tasty?
Delicious!
Red?
Red!
I'm glad we're together.
Original time. Salad time with you.
You can be cool and eat it.You can eat like a cool guy. - I'm not eating like a cool guy.
I don't eat cool. I don't eat cool.
Original time. With you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
I want to drink Tansan
Unit ice cream ammer live is over.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
I feel like I've done everything today.
It was nonstop, you know.
We didn't talk much today. Today.
You had to call me every single time.
Not that much.
It's because we don't get along with each other.
No, no, no.
We were just talking.
Because I wanted to tease you today.
That's not true.
If the four of us were like this...
Shut up.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm telling you, we've gone from nine songs to the current single.
And you know what? We've done the lead songs for the main album and everything, so that's 16 songs.
16 songs.
That's amazing.
It was amazing.
It was really nostalgic.
I think it was a great day.
I feel like I can go to bed right now. If I had a bed.
If we had a bed.
I slept here.
I can sleep without it.
I can sleep.
If I had a bed, I could sleep.
If you have a bed, you can sleep.
Shall we sleep?
And today's new clothes.
Yes, it's cute. It's cute.
It doesn't really fit in.
That's right. It's tight, tight, tight.
It's creaking.
That's amazing.
But it's been a while, right? It's been a while since you've felt this kind of lumpy feeling.
Yeah. Yes, it's true.
I can say I've been looking for a bigger, fluffier mask.
This is it.
It's amazing.
So, we have Marilee's and our 7th anniversary concert is coming up in March.
And we have our 7th anniversary concert in March.
I would like to keep on running.
I will do my best!
Gentle Hiimo.
Gentle hijo.
Eh, cute customer.